Longfield Park has a programme of activities throughout the year, and to give you a sample, this is what's happening in the next few days.
朗菲尔德公园全年都有活动，举个例子，这是在接下来的几天举行的活动。
On Monday you can learn about herbs, and how they've been used over the centuries.
你可以在周一学习草本植物，几个世纪以来，人们是如何使用它们的。
You'll start with a tour of our herb garden, practise the technique of using them as colour dyes for cloth,
你们会先从参观草本植物园开始，练习将它们用作衣服染料的手法，
and listen to an illustrated talk about their about their use in cooking and medicine.
参照图片聆听它们在烹饪和药材上的用途。
Then on Wednesday you can join local experts to discover the variety of insects and birds that appear in the evening.
然后，你可以在周三和当地专家一起研究在晚上出现的各种昆虫和鸟类。
We keep to a small number of people in the group, so if you want to go you'll need to phone the park ranger a few days ahead.
我们在这组上要限制人数， 所以如果你想参加，你需要提前几天给公园管理员打电话。
There's a small charge, which you should pay when you turn up.
这会收取少许费用，你来的时候要交费。
I'm sure you're all keen to help with the practical task of looking after the park, so on Saturday you can join a working party.
我敢肯定你们都希望帮助照看公园，所以你们可以在周六加入工作组。
You'll have a choice of all sorts of activities from planting hedges to picking up litter,
你们可以选择各种各样的活动，从种树篱到捡垃圾，
so you'll be able to change from one to another when you feel like it.
所以你们可以根据喜好而改变。
The rangers will be hard at work all day, but do come and join in, even for just a short while.
公园管理员整天都得努力工作，但是加入我们吧，即便是很短一段时间也可以。
One thing, though, is to make sure you're wearing something that you don't mind getting dirty or torn.
尽管有一件事是你们得穿不介意弄脏、弄破的衣服。